kudzuinteractive.com 2015-12-06

# Tillster Privacy Policy – Your Privacy Rights : Tillster

Effective Date 11/11/2013 (last updated 11/11/2013)

#### This Privacy Policy applies to our sites

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where the policy is located. This policy does not describe how we treat information we get from other sources. This includes information we get from our clients. By interacting with us, you consent to these practices.

#### We collect information from and about you

**We collect contact information.** For example, we might collect your name and email address if you contact us through the site. We might also collect your phone number.

**We collect information you submit or post.** We collect information when you contact us.

**We collect demographic information.** We may collect information like your gender and age. We may also collect your zip code. We might collect this when you contact us or enter a promotion.

**We collect other information.** If you use our website, we may collect information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us.

#### We collect information in different ways.

**We collect information directly from you.** For example, if you sign up for our emails. We also collect information if you contact us.

**We collect information from you passively.** We collect personal information about users over time and across different Web sites when a you use this Web site or service. We use tracking tools like browser cookies.

**We get information about you from third parties.** For example, social media platforms may also give us information about you.

#### We use information as disclosed and described here.

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** For example, we might use your information to respond to your customer feedback.

**We use information to improve our products and services.** We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

**We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.

**We use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. If you register with us, we may enroll you in our email newsletter.

**We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.** We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

#### We may share information with third parties.

**We will share information within the Tillster family of companies.**

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** For example, we share information with vendors who perform services for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites or send emails for us.

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

#### You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.** To stop receiving our promotional emails, email us at [privacy@www.tillster.com](mailto:privacy@www.tillster.com). Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions.

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies or other tracking tools. How you do so depends on the type of tool. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies. To control flash cookies, which we may use on certain websites from time to time, you can go [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). Why? Because flash cookies cannot be controlled through your browser settings. If you block cookies on your browser, certain features on our sites may not work. If you block or delete cookies, not all of the tracking activities we have described here will stop. Choices you make are both browser and device-specific.

**Our Do Not Track Policy** Some web browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature. This feature lets you tell websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. These features are not yet uniform across browsers. Our sites are not currently set up to respond to those signals.

#### These Sites and children.

Our sites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can [email us](mailto:privacy@www.tillster.com). You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children’s privacy on-line [here](http://www.business.ftc.gov/privacy-and-security/childrens-privacy).

#### We store information in the United States.

Information we maintain may be stored both within and outside of the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

#### We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

#### We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control.

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.

#### Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or if you would like to correct or update your information, you may contact us at:  
**Tillster, Inc**  
Attn: Privacy  
10070 Mesa Rim Rd.,  
San Diego, CA 92121  
Email: privacy@www.tillster.com

#### We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

© 2013 Tillster, Inc. All rights reserved.
